In this lesson, you will style the calculator to give it a clean, modern look.
So, we will keep the key part on logic exactly the same, we will only focus on improving
the design.
First, you will set a different background for the page and place the calculator in the
centre of the screen, both vertically and horizontally.
The calculator itself will also have a different background, a bigger size and some padding
and soft shadow, to make it look nicely.
Next, we will start improving the buttons, so each of them will be circular, with text
or symbol perfectly centered mode as it is currently, so it will be much better.
So, we will also add some hover effects for the buttons and we will change it depend on
the button time.
For example, it will depend on the control button, it is a digit or it is an operator
button, all of them will have different background colors.
So, by the end of this lesson, you calculate the view look professional and visually
balanced and keeps the same punch mode.
So, I suggest let it get started.
Let's switch to our compiler and I will present you the first one, I prepared.
So, I first ask, keep the keypad exactly the same as it has.
Use a light page background and dark calculator cards background, so we will have the opposite
of the background, we will be, it will be state dark, but it will dark grey background and
the calculator, sorry, the page background will be white and the calculator will be still
same dark grey background.
We will center the calculator as it all will set the fixed widths as 480 pixels, which
is a bit bigger than we will add some patterns, some rounded corners, some soft shadow and
etc.
So, I will use an ancient mode to exactly apply changes and let's see what you will get
at the result.
So, it will take some time to send your start to managing some CSS, also please keep in
mind that if you will use a different model, you might have a better result, for example,
if you use the cloud sonnet or some other models, like you might have the opening eye, another
model and of course, to use the models you need to have a plate plan, but you will have
a better result, so indeed, okay, it reads in the CSS file just to analyze what styles
to be already have here and let me close this preview, and in a while it will suggest
some changes, so let's wait a bit.
Also, if you use one of the premium model, you might get the faster results, so it's for
short.
Okay, we have some changes, it was changed, we changed only the one file, you see all
the files were changed, if we click, we'll see the red one, what was removed and the blue
one, what was added, okay, I'll click, keep all the changes and we'll switch to application,
when I see it looks better, almost better, so we'll fix the buttons in the next prompt,
what else I suggest you just to fix the layout because it's not centered, so I will say
it's, wait or up, it's not centered vertically, exit, so sometimes the guy doesn't keep
all details, sometimes forget something or just do mistakes, so we always need to validate
it and be ready to write some additional prompt to fix it, okay, now we see, he applied
some minimal hate for the application, it should be fixed, so it's centered now, it looks
much better, okay, great, let's now start with our next prompt, I will keep all the changes
you close the index CSS, and in the next prompt we'll work with the buttons, we'll make
them more beautiful, I'd like to make all buttons circular and the same size, just to be sure
AI doesn't broke it, I will center the text of symbol inside each button, I will also
range buttons in a grid, same as we have, I just repeat it for AI to doesn't broke it because
it can, I will equal spacing between them, so that it will carry about the position in
the buttons, not like we have, but like a strange it for the full width, and I will ask
use equal pattern for consistent look at some however effects, based on time, for example
the light gray for contour buttons, we have the contour button as AC, backspace, equal
and others, then we have orange for operator buttons, just operator and the gray for the
digits, okay, let's ask to implement the changes, you can always use JGBT to help you improve
your prompts, I did it always, especially if it's a first prompt, you'd like to write it
in details, you can share a screenshot, a JGBT or write it directly, and it will help to
improve and add more details, and then like AI will understand you better, okay, we have
some changes, but it's still working, okay, it adds some animations, some backgrounds, okay,
I am curious how it looks like, yeah, but let's wait a bit, if it's applied, all the changes,
okay, we see, all the changes was applied, yeah, we have a background, it's too big,
I would say, so let's ask make buttons, make buttons a bit smaller, a bit more, what else?
So I guess the background just looks fine, just, okay, let's ask to make buttons a bit
smaller, just, because it's too big buttons, too big spacing, okay, it did it, so it looks
much better, so we have beautiful buttons, okay, and I will see you in the next lesson,
where we'll start with the formatting of the numbers and some other things which are really
important for the users.
Okay, see you in the next lesson.